[{"Question": "\u201cWhiff waff\u201d and \u201cflim flam\u201d are alternate names for which sport?", "Options": ["Table Tennis", "Badminton", "Handball", "Basketball"], "Answers": "A"}, {"Question": "In modern Olympic Games which athletes commonly do not take part in the opening parade due to competition early the next day", "Options": ["Triathlon", "Swimmers", "Marathon runners", "Wrestlers"], "Answers": "B"}, {"Question": "Sailing (49er class) and Equestrian are the only two Olympic events (as at 2016) in which men and women can", "Options": ["Compete against each other", "Wear watches", "\u00a0Listen to iPods/personal stereos", "Take banned drugs (to counter motion sickness)"], "Answers": "A"}, {"Notes": "IOC has added five new sports to the programme for Tokyo 2020. It included baseball/softball, karate, skateboarding, sports climbing and surfing. The inclusion of the new sports will add 18 events and 474 athletes. The IOC considered a variety of factors when assessing the proposal, including the impact on gender equality and the youth appeal of the sports.", "Question": "The International Olympic Committee(IOC) has added how many new sports for the 2020 Olympics?", "Options": [8.0, 7.0, 5.0, 4.0], "Answers": "C"}, {"Question": "Which American sportsman has nickname \"The Baltimore Bullet\"?", "Options": ["Muhammad Ali", "Jesse Owens", "Babe Ruth", "Michael Phelps"], "Answers": "D"}, {"Question": "Name the Polish Olympian who sold his Rio medal to save life of a three year old boy suffering with cnacer.", "Options": ["Piotr Malachowski", "Natalia Madaj", "Rafa\u0142 Majka", "Wojciech Nowicki"], "Answers": "A"}, {"Notes": "Soviet gymnast Larisa Latynina, who earned 18 medals in the 1950s and 60s.", "Question": "Michael Phelps now has 28 medals in all Olympics, the most ever. But who has the second most?", "Options": ["Carl Lewis", "Mark Spitz", "Larisa Latynina", "Usain Bolt"], "Answers": "C"}, {"Question": "Which sport is not going to be a part of the Tokyo Games?", "Options": ["Mixed Martial Arts", "Skateboarding", "Sport Climbing", "Surfing"], "Answers": "A"}, {"Question": "When was the last time Team USA's basketball team didn't take gold?", "Options": [1972.0, 1998.0, 2004.0, "Never"], "Answers": "C"}, {"Question": "What is the distance of the marathon race in the Olympics?", "Options": ["21 miles 585 yards", "22 miles 855 yards\u00a0", "24 miles 835 yards\u00a0", "26 miles 385 yards"], "Answers": "D"}, {"Question": "\u00a0What do the five rings on the Olympic symbol represent?", "Options": ["The five oceans", "The five continents", "The five planets", "Five Greek Gods"], "Answers": "B"}, {"Question": "Who of the following was the first female Olympic champion?", "Options": ["Helen Jackson", "Charlotte Cooper", "Agnes Morton", "Louise Martin"], "Answers": "B"}, {"Question": "Which olympian has been nicknamed 'The Flying Fish'?", "Options": ["Michael Phelps", "Ussain Bolt", "Carl Lewis", "Mark Sptitz"], "Answers": "A"}, {"Question": "The greatest and most versatile player of all time, _______, not only just succeeded in American football and baseball but also while participating in basketball matches and various events of Olympic", "Options": ["Jesse Owens", "Babe Ruth", "Jim Thorpe", "Carl Lewis"], "Answers": "C"}]